A proper spy movie.
Kingsman: The Golden Circle is a action, adventure,
comedy film directed by Matthew Vaughn.
When an attack on the Kingsman headquarters takes place and a new villain rises, Eggsy and Merlin are
forced to work together with the American agency known as the Statesman to save the world.
Eggsy, played by Taron Egerton.
Harry Hart, played by Colin Firth.
Poppy, played by Julianne Moore.
Merlin, played by Mark Strong.
Princess Tilde, played by Hanna Alström.
Ginger, played by Halle Berry.
Kingsman: The Golden Circle is a 2017 British spy action comedy film
directed by Matthew Vaughn and written by Jane Goldman and Vaughn.
Based on the Millarworld comic book series The Secret Service (later retitled Kingsman) by Mark Millar and Dave Gibbons, in turn based on a concept by
Millar and Vaughn, the film is the sequel to Kingsman: The Secret Service (2014) and the second instalment in the Kingsman film series.
The film features an ensemble cast consisting of Colin Firth, Taron Egerton, Mark Strong, Sophie Cookson, Edward Holcroft, and Hanna Alström, who reprise
their roles from the first film, with Julianne Moore, Halle Berry, Pedro Pascal, Elton John, Channing Tatum, and Jeff Bridges joining the cast.
The film follows members of Kingsman needing to team up with their American counterpart, Statesman, after the Kingsman organization is crippled and the world is held hostage by Poppy Adams and
her drug cartel, "The Golden Circle."
Kingsman: The Golden Circle premiered in London on 18 September 2017 and was theatrically released in the United Kingdom on 20 September 2017.
It grossed $410 million worldwide against a budget of $104
million and received mixed reviews from critics.
A prequel, The King's Man, was released on 22 December 2021, while a
spin-off film, Argylle, was released on 1 February 2024.
The film explores themes of saving the world, spy, europe,
sequel, secret government organization.
The tone is lighthearted.